https://www.prairieband.com/pbcr-privacy-policy/

Application of This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to the prairieband.com website (the “PBCR website”) owned or operated by Prairie Band Potawatomi Entertainment Corporation (“PBPEC”), on behalf of Prairie Band Potawatomi Nation d/b/a Prairie Band Casino & Resort (“PBCR” and together with PBPEC, the “PBCR Group”). It is possible that now or in the future the PBCR website may be accessed through domain names in addition to the domain names listed above. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by the PBCR Group by means other than through the PBCR website.
Certain transactions and services offered while visiting the PBCR website may be processed or provided by other entities (collectively, the “Other Entities”) under contract with members of the PBCR Group, even though it appears that you may not have left the PBCR website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by Other Entities; except that PBPEC will treat information it receives about you from Other Entities under the terms of this Privacy Policy. The PBCR Group does not have any control over how Other Entities use information they collect about you. We encourage you to look for and review the privacy policy of the relevant Other Entity prior to providing private information to such Other Entity.
This site may contain links to outside websites. By accessing another website from the PBCR website, you hereby release us from any and all liability for your use of such link and website. We have no control over and are not responsible for the content that appears on these other websites. Once you access another website, be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you to look for and review the privacy policy of each and every website that you visit through a link or advertisement.
Collection of General Information
When you use the Internet, your web browser or client software may transmit certain information to the servers that host the websites you visit. The information may include the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, the capabilities and features of your computer, your geographic location, and your movement within and interaction with the website, including what pages you look at and what information you download. When you visit the PBCR website, PBPEC servers collect such information. PBPEC uses this information to generate aggregate statistics about visitors to the PBCR website.
Collection of Personally Identifying Information
The PBCR Group only collects personal information that you voluntarily provide to us or voluntarily provide to other entities who share that information with us. “Personal Information” is information through which you can be identified. The Personal Information that PBCR Group collects through the PBCR website or obtains from its Other Entities depends on the nature of your online activity, such as whether you make reservations, apply for employment online, make purchases online, request charitable donations online, or engage in online social gaming. Personal Information that Prairie Band Potawatomi Entertainment Corporation may collect from you directly or through other entities, includes your name, Players Club account number, address, email address, telephone number(s), fax number, birth date, gender, credit card information, purchase and reservation information and other information that you voluntarily provide. The Personal Information is collected by email, through online forms, and through your activities on the PBCR website.
Cookies and Similar Technology
The PBCR website uses cookie technology. A cookie is a small text file that contains information sent by a website that is saved on your hard disk or hard drive by your computer’s browser. Cookies store information that a website may need to personalize your experience and to gather website statistical data, such as which pages you visit, what material you download, your internet provider’s domain name and country, and the addresses of websites you visited immediately before, and after, visiting a particular website.
The PBCR website uses cookies to collect and store your preferences for viewing our site. In addition, the PBCR website uses cookies to provide a unique identifier to your computer so that we can generate statistics regarding usage of our site, such as the percentage of repeat visitors and other general statistics. We do not link non-Personal Information from cookies to Personal Information without your permission. Moreover, cookies used by the PBCR Group do not collect or store any Personal Information about you.
To browse the Internet and the PBCR website without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when each cookie is offered so that you can accept or reject each cookie. You may not be able to conduct some transactions or use some services on the PBCR website if you disable your browser from accepting cookies.
We may also use other standard Internet technologies, such as Flash technologies, Web beacons or pixel tags, and other similar technologies, to deliver or communicate with cookies and track your use of the PBCR website.
Use of Collected Information
The PBCR Group will use the information collected by us or Other Entities for the specific purposes for which you provided the information, as stated at the time of collection. The following are some other ways in which we may use your information to administer our business and provide you with the products and services you request:
to operate our Players Club program; for marketing purposes, including, but not limited to, notifying you of events, promotions and offers regarding products and services provided by us or our affiliates or other associated third parties;
to improve the products and services we provide you and develop new products and services;
to improve the PBCR website;
to track your use of the PBCR website for our internal market research;
to ask for your participation in our internal market research;
to generate aggregate statistical studies about our customers;
to process and fulfill reservations or purchases and make a record of reservations or purchases;
to enable us to contact you for confirmation or customer service after reservations or purchases are made or after you sign up for or participate in certain activities;
to respond to inquiries, complaints and other communications;
to cross-reference with other Personal Information that we have acquired about you or may acquire about you through other sources; for any other reason with your consent or as permitted or required by law.
Disclosure of Collected Information
Except as provided below, the PBCR Group will not sell, trade, or disclose to unaffiliated third parties any Personal Information obtained through the PBCR website or obtained from Other Entities, without your consent. Prairie Band Potawatomi Entertainment Corporation may disclose Personal Information: (1) to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; (2) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; (3) to protect and defend members of the PBCR Group, their subsidiaries and affiliates, and all of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, and partners, in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; (4) to enforce the terms of use of the PBCR website; (5) to prevent imminent physical harm; (6) to businesses that the PBCR Group may use for purposes of performing functions on behalf of PBPEC or PBCR, including Other Entities, such as companies that process credit card transactions; and (7) in connection with the sale, assignment, or transfer of any PBCR Group property or the PBCR website.
User Choice Regarding Providing Information
General information is collected whenever you browse the PBCR website. The PBCR website does not provide any means for opting out of providing general information when you browse this site. An example of general information would be noting the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site or advertisement.
You can browse the PBCR website without providing any Personal Information. However, providing Personal Information is required to use some of the services offered through the PBCR website, including, but not limited to, making hotel reservations, making purchases, requesting information, applying for employment, participating in online social gaming and requesting charitable donations.
You can opt out of receiving certain communications and offers. Opt out options will be indicated when they are available.
Access
The general information or Personal Information collected through the PBCR website or provided to us by Other Entities is not currently accessible to you, except that confirmation is provided for some transactions and services, such as reservations and purchases.
Security
General information and Personal Information collected by the PBCR website is stored on secure servers. The secure servers are protected by firewalls and other standard security procedures. The secure servers are not generally accessible by unauthorized third parties, but could become accessible in the event of a security breach.
For features on the PBCR website that require a login or password, it is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
Age Restrictions
Pursuant to applicable law, persons under the age of eighteen (18) are not permitted to gamble in, or loiter in the gaming areas of, the Prairie Band Casino & Resort. Similarly, the PBCR website is a general audience site intended only for persons over the age of 18. Please leave this site if you are under the age of 18. By continuing, you hereby release us, our subsidiaries and affiliates, from any and all liability for your use of, or access to, the PBCR website.
We will not rent rooms to persons under the age of 18. Any offers, contests, activities, or programs promoted are strictly limited to people over 18, unless otherwise indicated.
Persons younger than 18 years of age are not allowed to use the PBCR website, accept offers, or win contests, and we do not knowingly collect information from such persons. We reserve the right to verify age at any time for any reason and may decline to provide products, services or access rights to any person who does not have valid age identification.
Changes to Privacy Policy
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the PBCR website. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon such posting.
Contacting Us
If you have a privacy concern or question regarding us or this Privacy Policy and you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of the PBCR website, you should contact us through one of the following methods:
Email:
privacy@prairieband.com
Mail:
Prairie Band Casino & Resort 12305 150th Road Mayetta, KS 66509
General: (785) 966-7777
Toll Free: (888) PBP-4WIN
Sales: (785) 966-7742
